<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="moviesTittles">
        <item>Interstellar</item>
        <item>The Martian</item>
        <item>Avatar</item>
        <item>The life of Pi</item>
        <item>The Avengers</item>
    </array>

    <array name="moviesDescriptions">
        <item>In Earths future, a global crop blight and second Dust Bowl are slowly rendering the
            planet uninhabitable. Professor Brand (Michael Caine), a brilliant NASA physicist, is
            working on plans to save mankind by transporting Earths population to a new home via a
            wormhole. But first, Brand must send former NASA pilot Cooper (Matthew McConaughey) and
            a team of researchers through the wormhole and across the galaxy to find out which of
            three planets could be mankinds new home.
        </item>
        <item>When astronauts blast off from the planet Mars, they leave behind Mark Watney (Matt
            Damon), presumed dead after a fierce storm. With only a meager amount of supplies, the
            stranded visitor must utilize his wits and spirit to find a way to survive on the
            hostile planet. Meanwhile, back on Earth, members of NASA and a team of international
            scientists work tirelessly to bring him home, while his crew mates hatch their own plan
            for a daring rescue mission.
        </item>
        <item>On the lush alien world of Pandora live the Navi, beings who appear primitive but are
            highly evolved. Because the planets environment is poisonous, human/Navi hybrids,
            called Avatars, must link to human minds to allow for free movement on Pandora. Jake
            Sully (Sam Worthington), a paralyzed former Marine, becomes mobile again through one
            such Avatar and falls in love with a Navi woman (Zoe Saldana). As a bond with her
            grows, he is drawn into a battle for the survival of her world.
        </item>
        <item>After deciding to sell their zoo in India and move to Canada, Santosh and Gita Patel
            board a freighter with their sons and a few remaining animals. Tragedy strikes when a
            terrible storm sinks the ship, leaving the Patels teenage son, Pi (Suraj Sharma), as
            the only human survivor. However, Pi is not alone; a fearsome Bengal tiger has also
            found refuge aboard the lifeboat. As days turn into weeks and weeks drag into months, Pi
            and the tiger must learn to trust each other if both are to survive.
        </item>
        <item>When Thors evil brother, Loki (Tom Hiddleston), gains access to the unlimited power
            of the energy cube called the Tesseract, Nick Fury (Samuel L. Jackson), director of
            S.H.I.E.L.D., initiates a superhero recruitment effort to defeat the unprecedented
            threat to Earth. Joining Furys "dream team" are Iron Man (Robert Downey Jr.), Captain
            America (Chris Evans), the Hulk (Mark Ruffalo), Thor (Chris Hemsworth), the Black Widow
            (Scarlett Johansson) and Hawkeye (Jeremy Renner).
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="moviesImages">
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/b/bc/Interstellar_film_poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/c/cd/The_Martian_film_poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/b/b0/Avatar-Teaser-Poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/ml/5/57/Life_of_Pi_2012_Poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/4/4d/Avengers_Infinity_War_poster.jpg
        </item>
    </array>
</resources>