<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="moviesTittles">
        <item>Interstellar</item>
        <item>The Martian</item>
        <item>Avatar</item>
        <item>The life of Pi</item>
        <item>The Avengers</item>
    </array>

    <array name="moviesDescriptions">
        <item>In Earths future, a global crop blight and second Dust Bowl are slowly rendering the
            planet uninhabitable. Professor Brand (Michael Caine), a brilliant NASA physicist, is
            working on plans to save mankind by transporting Earths population to a new home via a
            wormhole. But first, Brand must send former NASA pilot Cooper (Matthew McConaughey) and
            a team of researchers through the wormhole and across the galaxy to find out which of
            three planets could be mankinds new home.
        </item>
        <item>When astronauts blast off from the planet Mars, they leave behind Mark Watney (Matt
            Damon), presumed dead after a fierce storm. With only a meager amount of supplies, the
            stranded visitor must utilize his wits and spirit to find a way to survive on the
            hostile planet. Meanwhile, back on Earth, members of NASA and a team of international
            scientists work tirelessly to bring him home, while his crew mates hatch their own plan
            for a daring rescue mission.
        </item>
        <item>On the lush alien world of Pandora live the Navi, beings who appear primitive but are
            highly evolved. Because the planets environment is poisonous, human/Navi hybrids,
            called Avatars, must link to human minds to allow for free movement on Pandora. Jake
            Sully (Sam Worthington), a paralyzed former Marine, becomes mobile again through one
            such Avatar and falls in love with a Navi woman (Zoe Saldana). As a bond with her
            grows, he is drawn into a battle for the survival of her world.
        </item>
        <item>After deciding to sell their zoo in India and move to Canada, Santosh and Gita Patel
            board a freighter with their sons and a few remaining animals. Tragedy strikes when a
            terrible storm sinks the ship, leaving the Patels teenage son, Pi (Suraj Sharma), as
            the only human survivor. However, Pi is not alone; a fearsome Bengal tiger has also
            found refuge aboard the lifeboat. As days turn into weeks and weeks drag into months, Pi
            and the tiger must learn to trust each other if both are to survive.
        </item>
        <item>When Thors evil brother, Loki (Tom Hiddleston), gains access to the unlimited power
            of the energy cube called the Tesseract, Nick Fury (Samuel L. Jackson), director of
            S.H.I.E.L.D., initiates a superhero recruitment effort to defeat the unprecedented
            threat to Earth. Joining Furys "dream team" are Iron Man (Robert Downey Jr.), Captain
            America (Chris Evans), the Hulk (Mark Ruffalo), Thor (Chris Hemsworth), the Black Widow
            (Scarlett Johansson) and Hawkeye (Jeremy Renner).
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="moviesImages">
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/b/bc/Interstellar_film_poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/c/cd/The_Martian_film_poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/b/b0/Avatar-Teaser-Poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/ml/5/57/Life_of_Pi_2012_Poster.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/sco/4/4d/Avengers_Infinity_War_poster.jpg
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="actorsImages">
        <item>
            https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Matthew_McConaughey_-_Goldene_Kamera_2014_-_Berlin.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fc/Matt_Damon_2013.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/de/Sam_Worthington_4%2C_2013.jpg
        </item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/de/Suraj_sharma_life_of_pi.jpg</item>
        <item>
            https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/The_Avengers_Cast_2010_Comic-Con_cropped.jpg
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="mainActors">
        <item>Matthew McConaughey</item>
        <item>Matt Damon</item>
        <item>Sam Worthington</item>
        <item>Suraj sharma</item>
        <item>Robert Downey Jr</item>
    </array>

    <array name="biographies">
        <item>Matthew David McConaughey was born on November 4, 1969, in Uvalde, Texas. His
            mother, Mary Kathleen "Kay"/"KMac" (née McCabe), is a former kindergarten teacher and
            published author who taught McConaughey. She was originally from Trenton, New
            Jersey.His father, James Donald "Jim" McConaughey, was born in Mississippi in
            1929 and raised in Louisiana, where he ran an oil pipe supply business; he played
            for the Kentucky Wildcats and the Houston Cougars college football teams. In 1953,
            Jim was drafted in the 27th round by the NFLs Green Bay Packers. He was released before
            the season began and never played an official league game in the NFL
        </item>
        <item>Damon was born in Cambridge, Massachusetts, the second son of stockbroker Kent Telfer
            Damon and Nancy Carlsson-Paige, an early childhood education professor at Lesley
            University. His father had English and Scottish ancestry, and his mother is of
            five-eighths Finnish and three-eighths Swedish descent (his mothers family surname had
            been changed from the Finnish "Pajari" to "Paige"). Damon and his family
            moved to Newton for two years. His parents divorced when he was two years old, and Damon
            and his brother returned with their mother to Cambridge, where they lived in a
            six-family communal house. His brother Kyle is now an accomplished sculptor and
            artist.
        </item>
        <item>Samuel Henry John Worthington is an Australian actor and writer. He portrayed Jake
            Sully in the 2009 film Avatar, Marcus Wright in Terminator Salvation, and Perseus in
            Clash of the Titans as well as its sequel Wrath of the Titans.
        </item>
        <item>Suraj Sharma is an Indian actor who made his debut with 2012 film Life of Pi. Directed
            by Ang Lee, Life of Pi was adapted from the novel of the same name, and earned him
            critical acclaim as well as a BAFTA Rising Star Award nomination. In 2014, he portrayed
            Aayan Ibrahim in season 4 of the Showtime series Homeland.
        </item>
        <item>Robert John Downey Jr. is an American actor, producer and singer. His career has been
            characterized by critical and popular notoriety in his youth, followed by a period of
            substance abuse and legal troubles, before a resumption of critical repute and
            resurgence of commercial success in middle age.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="releasesDates">
        <item>November 6, 2014</item>
        <item>September 24, 2015</item>
        <item>December 10, 2009</item>
        <item>January 3, 2013</item>
        <item>April 22, 2019</item>
    </array>

    <array name="actors">
        <item>Matthew McConaughey as Joseph Cooper. Anne Hathaway as Amelia Brand. Jessica Chastain
            as Murph Cooper. Mackenzie Foy as young Murph. Ellen Burstyn as old Murph. Matt Damon as
            Mann. John Lithgow as Donald. Michael Caine as Professor Brand. Casey Affleck as Tom
            Cooper. Timothée Chalamet as young Tom.
        </item>
        <item>Matt Damon. Mark Watney. Jessica Chastain. Kristen Wiig. Annie Montrose. Jeff Daniels.
            Michael Peña. Rick Martinez. Sean Bean. Kate Mara. Beth Johanssen. Sebastian Stan. Aksel
            Hennie. Alex Vogel. Chiwetel Ejiofor. Benedict Wong. Bruce Ng. Mackenzie Davis. Donald
            Glover. Rich Purnell. Nick Mohammed.
        </item>
        <item>Sam Worthington. Jake Sully. Zoe Saldana. Sigourney Weaver. Dr. Grace Augustine.
            Michelle Rodriguez. Trudy Chacón. Giovanni Ribisi. Joel David Moore. Norm Spellman. CCH
            Pounder. Wes Studi. Eytukan. Laz Alonso. Dileep Rao. Dr. Max Patel. Sean Anthony Moran.
            Private Fike. Jason Whyte. Scott Lawrence.
        </item>
        <item>Suraj Sharma as Piscine Molitor Pi Patel, age 16/17. Irrfan Khan as Pi, adult. Rafe
            Spall as The Writer. Tabu as Gita Patel, Pis mother. Adil Hussain as Santosh Patel,
            Pis father. Ayan Khan as Ravi Patel, Pis older brother, age 7. Gérard Depardieu as the
            Cook. Wang Po-chieh as Sailor. Jag Huang as Sailor.
        </item>
        <item>Robert Downey Jr. Actor | Iron Man. Chris Evans. Actor | The Avengers. Brie Larson.
            Actress | Room. Chris Hemsworth. Actor | The Avengers. Mark Ruffalo. Actor | The Kids
            Are All Right. Scarlett Johansson. Actress | Her. Karen Gillan. Actress | Selfie. Paul
            Rudd. Actor | Ant-Man.
        </item>
    </array>


</resources>